<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RealEstateManager</string>
    <string name="app_name_formated">Real Estate Manager</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="login_greetings">To whom have I the honor ?</string>
    <string name="continue_button">Continue</string>
    <string name="chose_someone">Chose Someone</string>
    <string name="you_have_to_chose_a_profile_to_continue">You have to chose a profile to continue</string>
    <string name="logout">Log Out</string>
    <string name="error">An error has occurred</string>
    <string name="darius">Darius</string>
    <string name="cassio">Cassio</string>
    <string name="lucian">Lucian</string>
    <string name="bard">Bard</string>
    <string name="nilah">Nilah</string>
    <string name="what_you_wanna_add">What do you want to add</string>
    <string name="estate">Estate</string>
    <string name="agent">Agent</string>
    <string name="agent_creation">Agent Creation</string>
    <string name="empty_text">Text could not be empty</string>
    <string name="agent_created">Agent created !</string>
    <string name="first_house_desc">This stunning modern house boasts an architectural design that combines sleek, clean lines with elegant simplicity. The exterior is characterized by a combination of smooth white render, large glass windows, and natural wood accents, creating a harmonious balance between modernity and warmth. The house features a flat or low-pitched roof, adding to its contemporary aesthetic.</string>
    <string name="house">House</string>
    <string name="schools">Schools</string>
    <string name="shops">Shops</string>
    <string name="parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="second_house_desc">Classic Victorian architectural style, infused with a sense of eerie grandeur and mystery. This imposing structure is located in a historic neighborhood, exuding an old-world charm that belies its more sinister history.</string>
    <string name="third_house_desc">A Parisian apartment typically embodies the essence of classic French elegance combined with modern chic. Nestled within a charming Haussmannian building, recognized for its stone facade, wrought iron balconies, and mansard roofs, the apartment exudes an air of historic sophistication.</string>
    <string name="apartment">Apartment</string>
    <string name="subway">Subway</string>
    <string name="fourth_house_desc">A New York apartment in the Upper East Side exudes a blend of contemporary luxury and timeless sophistication, characteristic of one of Manhattan\'s most prestigious neighborhoods. These apartments, often located in classic pre-war buildings or sleek modern high-rises, offer a unique urban living experience.</string>
    <string name="us_dollar_symbol">$</string>
    <string name="euro_symbol">€</string>
    <string name="change_currency">Change Currency</string>
    <string name="fifth_house_desc">"Nestled in the heart of lush, rolling hills, this magnificent Campaign House Estate offers a tranquil escape into nature's embrace. "</string>
    <string name="media">Media</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
</resources>